# **Rex Liu**

Mobile phone: 0466 154 382

Email Address: liurunxiao233@gmail.com

Personal Website: https://rex-l-rx.github.io/Resume support/

#### ■ PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Entry-level IT Support professional. Recently completed the Google IT Support Professional Certificate - a hands-on program that covers troubleshooting, customer service, networking, operating system administration, and security. Currently Working as an IT Support Specialist from 01/2023.

## ■ Working Experience

# Yoo's Technology Pty Ltd | Melbourne, VIC | IT Support Technician

01/2023 - Present

- Provide technical support to customers, including PC hardware and software troubleshooting
- Assist with general IT support tasks

• Setup new PCs with appropriate software

# Navigator Education Group Pty Ltd, | Hobart, TAS | ICT Course Adviser

02/2020 - 11/2021

- Assisting students in studying ICT courses, with a focus on web development and C# programming, at UTAS.
- Provided guidance and support to students

#### ■ Skills

#### **Technical Skills**

- Operating System administration (Window and Linux)
- Computer networking
- Software management
- Troubleshooting (Network, Desktop, Laptop and Smart Phone)
- Network security
- Resource monitoring

- Routing concepts (TCP/IP, Subnetting, DNS, DHCP)
- VPNs and proxies
- Implementing/managing directory services (AD)
- Data management and recovery
- IT security
- Remote Support tools such as RDP, Team Viewer.
- Office 365, Azure AD, AD

#### **Soft Skills**

- Excellent communication and interpersonal skills
- Customer service

- Strong attention to detail
- Quick learner and highly adaptable

#### Education

# Google on Coursera | Google IT Support Professional Certificate

03/2024

University of Tasmania | Master of Information Technology

02/2019 - 12/2020

#### Australian Working Right

190 Permanent Residence Visa, Unlimited Work Entitlement

# References available upon request.